If you're having trouble with an episodic talk, get a laugh by talking about ________.
What? There's a great answer to that question?
There is?
Like the reason why you were able to make it to the end.
I never thought I'd be the last first-year student.
What? That's a really good story.
What? No, it's true.
This time, we're going to do the ever-popular "Paysen Series"!
It's great!
And Mr. Niuji came last time.
In front of Mr. Niuji is Mr. Otani.
In front of Mr. Otani is Mr. Bastard.
Lior came, and Shin-Uchi-san came.
Hayashi cried a lot.
At the end, we just shook hands and that was it.
But it was memorable, wasn't it?
Yes, it was a great memory.
And Takahashi likes Nogizaka-san.
But he's not feeling well.
He was a big fan of Shinguji-san.
I was a big fan of hers.
But I couldn't come to the show because of the other reason, so I was crying.
I guess we were crying in different ways.
No, it's a little bit amazing this time too.
This time, he's going through the most stuff.
I see.
There are things you can only learn from this person.
Yes, there are.
Also, he's a great speaker.
That's true.
He really got in my line of sight.
He looked at me like he didn't like me at all.
Stop saying that.
I can talk like crazy.
So, I'd like to invite our guest.
This is our guest. Come on in.
Hello. - Hello.
Here she is.
I'm Minami Misato Kishi, a 24/7 rebel.
Pleased to meet you.
Members
I look forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
You haven't said that in a while.
You haven't said it in a long time. I haven't said it in years.
I'm a senior idol now, everyone.
The AKBs are already of the same generation.
We can't stop trembling either.
I'm glad.
That's nice.
Takanashi-san seems a little disappointed.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's not true.
From the moment you came in, you had a gogo-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go-go aura behind you.
It's true.
Thank you.
But I'm really a little nervous today.
Really?
I've seen you and Otani-san...
I saw Shinnai-san's episode, too.
Everyone's talk was so intense.Everyone's talk was very intense.
They talked about all kinds of things, you know, like what they were talking about at the time.
I talked about it all on Talk Survivor.
You put it all out there?
I let it all out at Yuka Iga's place.
Minehiko, you were trying to win the game.
My drawers were empty.
That's right, I was trying to win the game.
That's right.
But I would like to ask you some questions this time.
I would like to ask you a few questions.
Do any of you feel that you are negative?
No, there are quite a few.
In the last recording.
My hand went up a little bit.
I was very relieved, so there were about four, oh, five people.
You see, Nagamatsu, your hands are so negative that they are not raised anymore.
He wants to raise his hand, but he can't. He's so negative.
Hineno, what do you think?
Well, I think it's always
Always.
All the time.
Even when I'm talking to people.
I'm always thinking, "Oh, they just thought of me this way...
I think about every single word.
Minus, minus, minus, minus.
I always live in the negative.
What about you, Nagamatsu?
I don't think people think I'm too negative.
Even if my manager says something about me, I tell him I'm fine.
But when I go home alone...
I see. So you are secretly negative.
That's a pattern you can't let out.
I also have a negative side.
It's because of my negativity that I'm here now.
I've been in the entertainment business for a long time because of my negativity.
Because of my negativity, I've developed the ability to think about what people think of me.
I think I'm here now because I've developed the ability to use my art.
I see.
I'm really nervous today.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if I'm...
I'm just not confident enough to leave something for you guys.
I brought some sheet masks that I produced, and I was wondering if I could pass them out.
Sheet masks?
I'm sorry.
Oh, you produced them?
I'm producing.
Sheet masks.
If you don't mind.
There should be a letter with this.
You can bring it to me if you want.
We have a connection.
I feel like an auntie.
Thank you.
Please use it.
I'll give you a break today.
I'll do my best.
Even if it's not the talk after this.
If we're done with this, I'll go back to handing out sheet masks.If I'm done with this, I'll go back to handing out sheet masks.
I'll do my best, though.
I'm not a trial runner.
But I'm always thinking about what I can do.
I'm always thinking about it.
I'm a negative person.
That's why I'm here today to talk about how to get along in life.
I'd like to talk a little about what I want to tell you today.
But to begin with, you're a bright star...
It took you a long time to sell AKBs, right?
That's right.
Quite a bit.
Is that so?
Because my contract with the record company was cut once.
What?
That's right.
So that's why all the AKB's are so tough?
So you've been through a lot.
The first concert was... how many people were there?
Seven.
Ehhhh...
AKB...
Fans could move with them in the audience as they closed the show.
There were no people there.
There was such a time, wasn't there?
Yes, there was.
We really didn't have enough customers.
That's why we had a contract with Sony at first.
And then Sony cut the contract.
So you moved to King Records.
That's right.
And since it sold well at King Records.
The title of the best version released by Sony
"The Fish That Got Away.
Wow!
That's interesting.
And then AKB sold well
King Records
They made some kind of apology to Sony.
So they decided to give Nogizaka a shot at Sony, too.
I've heard this story.
That's what Akimoto-san and the others are saying.
I'm sure you understand.
I'm sure he understands.
Amazing.
They cut my contract.
So, with that in mind...
I'd like to ask you about some of the things that happened.
So this time...
I'd like to talk about this project.
Learn from Minegishi Paisen
It's because he's negative that he understands
Idle city clerk
So, here we go.
The first question is a quiz about location shooting in variety shows.
Here is the question
When I'm on location, I finish 00 very quickly.
What is the word in this 00?
Let's raise your hands from those who know.
Yes, Fujisaki.Yes, Fujisaki
Bathroom.
Aah!
But that's the kind of behavior
That's the nuance of it.
The way you feel...
Yes, Takahashi
meeting
That's right.
You should listen slowly, that's right.
Come on, yes, Hayashi
Pedestrian crossing.
I'll cross the pedestrian crossing as soon as possible.
It's dangerous to walk while talking.
Or running.
It's a traffic law.
Yes, that's important, too.
Saito
The waiter's story
The shopkeeper's story
He says it's important.
Listen to her.
Roke, that's the most important thing.
You've got to bring it out. That's...
You have to listen to the waitress.
I said yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, I said yes.
Yes, yes, whisper.
Put on the sunscreen
Wear sunscreen
Seasonal
Summer only!
Big, big
We all did it today
If you have, if you know, yes, Imina!
Meal
Meals.
Quickly.
Meal, well, the way I think about it is almost the same...
But because I'm a girl...
You have to be a little conscious of it.
Yes, Yoshimura.
Makeup
Yes, yes, makeup is the same.
Makeup, it's the same thing.
Right?
Yes, Takanashi.
Get dressed.
You're right.
Yes, this is...
A change of clothes.
Yes, that's right.
What does this mean?
It means that...
Because of the negativity.
I don't know if I should be spending your time and making you wait.
I don't know if it's okay for me to make you wait.
Anyway, I change quickly.
I'm usually dressed in about 30 minutes.Maybe 30 minutes, 35 minutes.
35 minutes or something like that.
I think I'll really only be gone for about 5 minutes.
But I'll be back in about five minutes.
That's fast.
It won't take more than 5 minutes.
Wow.
I asked her not to take too much time to reapply my makeup.
I'm very conscious of not taking up too much of other people's time.
Oh...
If it was Kanna Hashimoto, you wouldn't have to worry about that.
I really don't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Maybe Minegishi-san too
No, that's probably...
Oh, no, I'm not in character
I'll probably roll it up when it's quicker.
I thought it would make you happy.
If the staff winds it up, it's the only way to get the location.
Has anyone ever told you that?
It's been hard to get them to notice.
But last year, Mr. Tanaka of Angers finally told me about it on the radio.
Mr. Tanaka of Angers talked about it on the radio.
Oh, about all of Minegishi...
He said that Minegishi is on standby early.
Yes, sir.
How did it come about?
Who among you lovebirds is slow in getting dressed?
Late.
Oh, Fujisaki.
You're wearing a Don Quijoten T-shirt.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
It's a don Quijoten T-shirt.
It took me a long time to get the costumes.
Last time at the festival, it was like a last minute door-burner.
It was last minute.
Everyone around here thinks you're a little slow.
That's right... even before a photo shoot.
I would take my hair down until the last minute.
I'd wonder which one was better.
Does that mean you have to make a quick decision?
I spray my bangs down and make sure they don't move.
I have to have a feeling that I can't move my hair.
You have to have that kind of mindset.
I think it's a bit of a downside to make your co-stars wait.
It's a bit of a downside, I think.
Well, I don't mind if you're late now.
It's true that when I was an AD, I was a new talent and I was fixing my makeup in the middle of the hallway.
I was fixing my makeup in the middle of the hallway.
The type of talent that everyone avoids.
That's gone now.
We never worked with them.
These people are disappearing.
And I...
I saw Sakuma on TV.
I made the stylist carry my heels.
I had to wear slippers to the set.
Soft slippers.
Actresses and celebrities who have to put them back on.
Kurosawa-san said, "I don't like it.After Mr. Kurosawa said something like, "I don't like it.
I'm sure you'll be wearing heels from the dressing room.
I see.
People are watching, right?
That's right.
That's why I have to take care of myself.
I'm fully equipped.
But we don't get grouped together as a staff.
We'll share it with the team.
No group?
We don't get in groups.
Not at first.
At first, we'll fight the same game.
That's very important.
In the hallway, we're supposed to be on a flat surface.
It's an unspoken agreement.
We'll make a path.
Yes, we're doing that.
Well, this is...
I'm talking about something much deeper.
Be careful.
This will come back to haunt you, I promise.
You'll remember it someday.
The second question is mainly for talk shows and such, but here's the question.
If you are having trouble with an episodic talk, make people laugh by talking about ________.
What is the word that goes in this circle?
Is there such a wonderful answer?
Is there?
Okay, then...
I'll tell you a story about how I was hurt.
Well, yes...
That's part of it, too.
But I think it's something unique to you.
Yes, Fujisaki
Laughing at Sakuma's topic
Correct.
You're so fast!
Amazing.
We're ex-AKB48, after all...
AKB48 and Mr. Ruff Ruff have one thing in common
The producer is the most famous person in the world.
He already has name value.
There's no way we can avoid using him.
I see.
So when you were attacked, you talked a lot about Akimoto-san.
He's always kind to Akimoto when he's in trouble.
We always include Mr. Akimoto just once.
What do you mean by "episodes of Akimoto's kindness in times of trouble"?
For example, when she announced her marriage...
For example, when I announced my marriage... people would ask me if I said anything about Akimoto's kindness.
Because they want to make news.
I told Akimoto that I'm glad you got married.
Miminkishi couldn't be the center of AKB.
But she found someone who can make her the center of the group.
Good story.
I thought it was Akimoto who chose her as the center, like
Good copy.
It was probably the most popular copy in the history of press conferences.
I'm sure you heard that.
The history of press conferences in Japan.
What do you have? Like Mr. Sakuma's episodic talk.What do you guys have? Like Sakuma's episode talk.
Hayashi
Before we recorded last time, Sakuma was clacking away on his computer
and he was grinning.
I asked him what he was doing.
He said he was watching what I edited.
How embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing.
He said he loves himself.
I love myself, don't you?
I love what I made.
I love my work.
It's good.
Anything else? What else?
You wrote down a lot of advice that was given to you.
So, do you remember anything that was said to you? Sakuma.
I might have.
Saito
There was a time when I was having a hard time doing well in this YouTube recording.
I was having a hard time to make it interesting.
I talked to Sakuma-san about it.
I talked to Sakuma-san about it, and he told me that idols can enjoy the process of not being good at something.
I talked to Mr. Sakuma about it, and he told me that I should show it more, because people would enjoy the process.
He told me that I should show that more.
That's a really nice story.
He's such a kind person.
He's not that kind?
What do you think?
It's going to be an article in Model Press, isn't it?
Like the words of salvation from Ms. Sakuma.
I'm sure it will.
It's all over the Internet news.
You should use everything you can get your hands on.
Not just me.
I've met people, people who came here, and even Mitsubishi-san today.
The words I've received from people like that.
You should use whatever you can.
You could say, "Mr. Mitsubishi, you told me this today, so I'm doing this," or something like that.
Do you have contact information for Mr. Sakuma and the riffraff?
I don't know.
Mr. Akimoto's contact information?
I knew you knew his contact information, LINE, and so on.
When I was running out of material, I would ask him questions.
How am I these days?
What do you think I should do?
He told me that Akimoto-san was amazing.
There are hundreds of people in Nogizaka and AKB combined.
Do you know them all?
Not all of them, but he's on line with a lot of them.
Isn't that great?
But when you ask her something like that, she responds.
They get back to me. They really do.
He's looking right at it.
He replies quickly.
That's great, Akimoto-san.
Akimoto-san is, you know, amazing and scary.
Next, we'll go home.
Home coming!Going home edition!
It's time to go home!
It's important to be on your way home.
So, here is the problem.
I, Mr. Mineki...
What is it that I, Mr. Mineki, do after every recording?
Yes, I knew it.
After every recording.
Seven! I give out packets to everyone.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
The one we just did.
Exactly the same thing.
I'll leave a message.
I had an awesome time today!
Please read this again.
It was a fun recording.
Karina Maruyama is doing it, right?
Indeed.
Karina Maruyama's writing
I seriously don't get it.
It's indecipherable.
Something that came from the right
The one coming from the left
was overtaken by something that came from the left.
It was a kulbush.
I often say
This is great, isn't it?
What's this?
Okay, who gets it?
Takanashi.
I'm going backstage to check if there's any hair on the floor.
I'll check and go home.
But it's not the same.
That's important, too.
You should do it.
Yoshimura
I'll bring back as much Kettering as I can.
Ha-ha-ha.
I won't leave it behind.
That's true.
The parting of the ways, I mean.
You mean when you say goodbye to your staff?
Yes, Saito.
Hugs.
That's too much.
Okay, Hibino.
I'm going to ask him how he feels about the show.
I'm going to ask him to remember my name.
I'm going to call out your name a lot.
Minami Inagishi, how was it?
That's too negative.
I can't say that much.
If you don't say anything, it's just silence.
It's not a word.
If I had to say where...
Elevator.
Takanashi.
He's seeing me off in the elevator.
I'll close it quickly.
It's a little rude.I'm going to be a little rude.
I'm tempted to leave.
But...
When the elevator closes.
You bow until it closes.
That's correct.
Keep bowing until the elevator closes.
Until the elevator closes.
It's good for my mental health.
When the recording went well.
If I did that...
It went well.
If you do it all the way to the close
You can see how humble he is, can't you?
On the other hand, if it didn't go so well
I don't get to see the staff that much.
I don't want him to tell me how my day went.
I don't want him to tell me, and I can't ask him.
I don't want you to tell me how I did today, and I can't ask.
I don't make eye contact with them.
I just say, "I'm sorry.
That's all.
You did say thank you, didn't you?
She's sorry, but...
But you don't have to look her in the eye until the end.
I can go home.
To protect my mentality.
I bow all the way to the end.
I do this to protect my mentality.
It makes me look like a righteous person.
May I see your example?
The recordings I've done.
A recording I've had my whole life.
Yes, please.
Oh, thank you very much for your time. Thank you very much.
Well, excuse me. Thank you for your time.
Yes, it's closed
Ha-ha-ha
The second year is not the same as the first year, so you might want to lower it.
That's how gala it's going to be.
I wonder how we'll feel.
We'll bow down a lot, too.
You're bowing a lot?
Yes, we bow a lot.
When you're not receiving, do you clench your teeth a lot?
I can see that.
When it looked like fun, I was really clenching.
I had already done it three times, and I kept my head down until I got to the first one.
We both cried a little.
Did you get it?
No, I didn't.
No, the guy in front of us was Mr. Hyokkori Han, and he was bouncing all over the place.
It was really bad off the set when we couldn't do it anymore and things didn't go well.
That was terrible.
Just try it for a minute.
When it looks like fun
When it looks fun.
When it looks like fun, I'll be the producer.
That's what a producer does, right?That's what producers are for, right?
He thinks it's okay that he didn't do so well, but he's just trying to cheer you up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's really okay.
Good night.
I'm totally fine. And the editing.
No, it is.
Because the front was hick.
No, but it was totally fine.
I think it's getting really interesting, totally.
Editing.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
Once, kumquat.
This is really, really serious.
How's that? Something from Ruff Ruff.
Is this a good time?
I'd like to ask you something.
Yoshimura...
Well, you've been...
You're so cute!
You were there from the first student to the last, weren't you?
Does that mean that you decided to stay with us from the beginning?
Or did you just realize that you were going to stay until the end?
How did you decide to stay until the end, and why?
I didn't think that I would stay until the end.
I didn't think I would be the last member of the first group at all.
But 10 years ago, an irregular incident happened to me.
I had my head shaved.
It was an incident or something like that.
I didn't want people to think that's why I quit.
I didn't want people to think that I quit.
But I didn't want people to think that I quit because I wasn't good enough as an idol.
I decided not to graduate until I could send everyone off with a smile.
Ten years had passed.
Oh, really?
That's a really good story!
No, it's true.
And after that, I was a member of Team 4 and other 1PB members who are now active in the industry.
It was a time when they were called the next generation.
There was a time when we were working together to nurture the younger generation.
You can't talk about AKB without Minegis.
You know, there are good things and bad things in an idol's life.
What advice can you give to the girls based on all of that?
What advice would you give to them?
Yeah, I don't know.
I think it's very important to save money without turning your back on the bad things.
For example, there was a live-action version of an original story that I modeled for, and instead of me, it was Acchan who starred in it.
It happened.
I was so frustrated that I wanted to tear my hair out.
I was so frustrated that it wasn't me.
I never thought that 10 years later
I never thought that 10 years later, the day would come when the whole world would be laughing at me
I never thought it would happen.
I thought that if I kept putting away all the pain and frustration
I think that one day you will become a Buddha.
I think it's better to save them without forgetting.
Let's review it together.
That word
Let's go!Let's go!
Let's go!
Don't turn away from something you don't like, save it.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
I was nervous. I was very nervous.
I was worried whether I conveyed my message well or not,
But I was very happy that they listened to me with straight eyes.
Thank you very much, everyone at Ruff Ruff for today.
I think there will probably be more difficult and sad times in my idol career.
At such times, there may be days when I want to escape to alcohol,
But when you go to a pub or a bar, please be careful not to take pictures with strangers.
I will continue to support you.
This is Minami Kaigan.
But she taught me an important part of being an idol.
I'm sorry, but I often felt that I was thinking the same thing as you.
On the other hand, I had no idea that Minegi did what she did because of her negativity.
I learned a lot because I came to think that I should think this way too.
I learned a lot.
I heard that they are lowering the elevator.
I think he needs to be more flexible.
Sure, soft is soft.
I'll start with flexibility.
Remember what we reviewed?
The last one?
Se-no.
No, really.
Don't turn away, don't look away, don't look at me, don't look at me.
Isn't that good?
Oh, that's nice.
Thank you for watching to the end!
This time, it's a cat version.
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan
miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow miaow
Nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia
mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia mia
squishy squishy squishy squishy squishy
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow!
meow
mia~~